[ music ]
[ música ]
You want these people.
Usted quiere a esas personas.
They order your products, sign up for your services,
Compran sus productos, solicitan sus servicios,
enroll in your classes, read your opinions,
se inscriben en sus clases, leen sus opiniones,
and watch your videos.
y miran sus vídeos.
You'll never see them, but they know you- through your website.
Usted nunca los ve, pero ellos le conocen a través de su sitio web.
Or maybe not.
O quizás no.
Your website's visitors aren't a faceless mass of identical mouse-clickers
Los visitantes de su web no son una masa informe de clicladores idénticos
but a vibrant community of individuals
sino una comunidad vibrante de indivíduos
with varying tastes, styles, and abilities.
con distintos gustos, estilos, y habilidades.
This includes people with disabilities.
Esto incluye personas con discapacidad.
[Terrill] It's important for web designers and developers
[Terrill] Es importante tanto para diseñadores como para desarrolladores
to realize that what they see currently on their computer,
darse cuenta de que lo que ellos ven en su ordenador,
at their resolution, with their browser and their operating system
con su resolución, con su navegador y su sistema operativo
is not going to be necessarily the same thing that everybody else sees.
no es necesariamente lo que todos los demás ven.